Teeth Whitening by Jean [unleashedART.com]

• Credits: Stock image by sxc.hu

• How to install the action:

   Double click the .atn file and PS should add the action to your library automatically. 
   At least this works in newer versions of PS.

   Alternative method:
   1. Put the .atn file from the zip in a directory of your choice. It does not need to be in the Photoshop directory.
   2. Choose Load Actions from the Actions palette menu.
   3. Select the action set file from the directory you saved it.
   4. Click Load.
   5. Have fun.